robertmstanley.com 2016-10-28

# RMS - Robert M Stanley Privacy - RMS

Privacy Policy

This statement discloses the privacy practices for robertmstanley.com, (”robertmstanley.com”).

When signing up for our services, you may be asked to provide information about you. All of the information is collected so that we can ensure that we can communicate with you as requested. Our privacy statement as set forth below is written so that you can understand exactly what we do and don’t do with your information.

robertmstanley.com collects user submitted information such as name and email address exclusively for this sites newsletter.

Collected email addresses are also used to send updates or news regarding the service. You may choose not to receive this type of email by opting-out of future robertmstanley.com modifications. All notification emails and newsletters will contain instructions for opting out of those communications in the future.

robertmstanley.com may use cookies to store visitors preferences and to record session information to better the visitors experience and potentially better the advertising and marketing promotions relevance.

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.  
* Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on visits to this site.  
* You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

robertmstanley.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on the robertmstanley.com family of websites.

Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time.

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, robertmstanley.com will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process; (2) to enforce the robertmstanley.com Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. robertmstanley.com reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of robertmstanley.com or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest.

Changes in Our Privacy Policy

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.

Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us – http://robertmstanley.com/contact/
